<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meaningful Movies</string>
    <string name="button_recommend">New recommendation</string>
    <string name="button_top12">Top 12 must see</string>
    <string name="button_history">History</string>
    <string name="button_saved">Saved for later</string>
    <string name="button_search">Search for a movie</string>
    <string name="rate">Rate</string>
    <string name="character_strength">Choose up to 4 character strengths</string>
    <string name="recommendation">Based on your chosen strengths, we recommend the following movies</string>
    <string name="rate_movie">Rate the movie</string>
    <string name="rate_enjoyable">How enjoyable was the movie for you?</string>
    <string name="rate_meaningful">How meaningful was the movie for you?</string>
    <string name="saved">Movies saved for later</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="rate_cs">Choose 4 character strengths that you encountered</string>
    <string name="results">Results for</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="search_input">Search a movie</string>

    <string name="info">Info</string>
    <string name="appreciation">I recognize, emotionally experience, and appreciate the beauty around me and the skill of others.</string>
    <string name="bravery">I act on my convictions, and I face threats, challenges, difficulties, and pains, despite my doubts and fears."</string>
    <string name="creativity">I am creative, conceptualizing something useful, coming up with ideas that result in something worthwhile.</string>
    <string name="curiosity">I seek out situations where I gain new experiences without getting in my own or other people\'s way.</string>
    <string name="fairness">I treat everyone equally and fairly, and give everyone the same chances applying the same rules to everyone.</string>
    <string name="forgiveness">I forgive others when they upset me and/or when they behave badly towards me, and I use that information in my future relations with them.</string>
    <string name="gratitude">I am grateful for many things and I express that thankfulness to others.</string>
    <string name="honesty">I am honest to myself and to others, I try to present myself and my reactions accurately to each person, and I take responsibility for my actions.</string>
    <string name="hope">I am realistic and also full of optimism about the future, believing in my actions and feeling confident things will turn out well.</string>
    <string name="humility">I see my strengths and talents but I am humble, not seeking to be the center of attention or to receive recognition.</string>
    <string name="humor">I approach life playfully, making others laugh, and finding humor in difficult and stressful times.</string>
    <string name="judgement">I weigh all aspects objectively in making decisions, including arguments that are in conflict with my convictions.</string>
    <string name="kindness">I am helpful and empathic and regularly do nice favors for others without expecting anything in return.</string>
    <string name="leadership">I take charge and guide groups to meaningful goals, and ensure good relations among group members.</string>
    <string name="love">I experience close, loving relationships that are characterised by giving and receiving love, warmth, and caring.</string>
    <string name="learning">I am motivated to acquire new levels of knowledge, or deepen my existing knowledge or skills in a significant way.</string>
    <string name="perseverance">I persist toward my goals despite obstacles, discouragements, or disappointments.</string>
    <string name="perspective">I give advice to others by considering different (and relevant) perspectives and using my own experiences and knowledge to clarify the big picture.</string>
    <string name="prudence">I act carefully and cautiously, looking to avoid unnecessary risks and planning with the future in mind.</string>
    <string name="self_regulation">I manage my feelings and actions and am disciplined and self-controlled.</string>
    <string name="social_intelligence">I am aware of and understand my feelings and thoughts, as well as the feelings of those around me.</string>
    <string name="spirituality">I feel spiritual and believe in a sense of purpose or meaning in my life; and I see my place in the grand scheme of the universe and find meaning in everyday life.</string>
    <string name="teamwork">I am a helpful and contributing group and team member, and feel responsible for helping the team reach its goals.</string>
    <string name="zest">I feel vital and full of energy, I approach life feeling activated and enthusiastic.</string>


</resources>
